eurohockeytv.org 2019-04-18

# EHTV Privacy Policy 24

      EHTV
Privacy Policy
24th May 2018
    Privacy Notice –

1.    Introduction
2.    European Hockey Federation (owners of EHTV) (hereafter EHTV) respects your privacy
      and personal data. This Privacy Notice (hereinafter referred to as “Notice”) explains how
      we process your personal data when you register for our services and browse on our
      Website. Personal data means any information which allows EHTV to directly or indirectly
      identify you.
2.1.  This Notice applies where EHTV acts as a controller of the personal data being collected
      and processed from our Website and. This means that this Notice applies where EHTV
      determines the purposes and means of the processing of the personal data.
2.2.  The personal data collected and processed by EHTV during your registration and access
      to our Website and App will be processed in accordance with the EU General Data
      Protection Regulation (hereinafter referred to as the “GDPR”) and with any other
      applicable privacy and data protection laws.
2.3.  The EHTV Website may contain links to websites of third-parties which are not covered
      by this privacy Notice. EHTV does not accept any responsibilities or liabilities for third-
      party websites.
2.4.  We strongly encourage you to take some time to read this Notice in full. If you do not
      agree to this Notice, we kindly request you not to provide us with your personal data.
3.    Who is EHTV?
3.1.  EHTV, owned by the EHF is a sports video platform which provides sports fans and
      content partners across the globe with the best videos from the world of hockey.
      EHTV furthermore can provide sports fans with news, statistics, live tickers and other
      content in hockey.
When this Notice mentions “we,” “us,” or the “Company,” it refers to the controller of your data
under this Notice, namely the EHTV (registration number 0884335538 1-2 Avenue Des Arts,
Brussels, 1210) with which you had, have or will have a business relationship or that otherwise
decides which of your data are collected and how they are used.
4.    What Personal Data Do We Collect?
4.1.  When registering for EHTV services, we may collect any information in which the services
      user can be identified. You can find below the personal data which we collect
      automatically, the personal data which is provided to us and the personal data which is
      collected from other sources.

4.2.   Automatically Collected Personal Data
4.2.1. In order to provide certain functionalities, when you access our Website, we may collect
       your IP address. In addition, we make use of cookies to better understand how you use
       our Website.
4.2.2. More information can be found in Section 4.1 and Section 6 of this Notice.
4.3.   Personal Data Provided to Us by You
4.3.1. When you register for our services, we collect different categories of personal data,
       depending on what service you decide to sign up for:
  For our EHTV, we collect your email address, your age range and the country of where your
   IP address is coming from
  For our newsletter service, we collect your email address and only deliver to those who have
   opted in to receive this service
  For our browser push-notification service, we collect your IP address
4.4.   When providing us with your personal data, EHTV kindly requests you to refrain from
       supplying us with any additional unsolicited personal data. In particular, EHTV requests
       you to refrain from supplying us with personal data relating to:
  Your racial and ethnic origin, and/or;
  Your political opinions, and/or;
  Your religious and philosophical beliefs, and/or;
  Your trade union membership, and/or;
  Data concerning your health, and/or;
  Data concerning your sex life or sexual orientation.
5.     How We Process Your Data?
5.1.   For What Purposes Do We Process Your Personal Data?
There are several reason why we use your personal data. In the most cases, it is about
measuring your behavior on our Website and, based on that, create personalized experiences,
both from a content as well as from an advertising point of view. More specifically, the purposes
are:
 For measuring on how users browse and behave on our Website
 For notifying you in case you participated in a prize game
 For serving personalized advertising to our users in order to increase the accuracy of our
   advertising

5.2.   On What Legal Grounds Do We Process Your Data?
       In order to process your personal data, we may rely on the different legal grounds,
       including:
5.2.1. Your consent, insofar as it is legally required or permitted. If we rely on your consent as
       a legal basis for processing your personal data, you may withdraw your consent at any
       time. This right is further specified in Section 13.9 of this Notice.
5.2.2. The necessity to establish a contractual relationship with you and to perform our
       obligations under the concerned contract.
5.2.3. The necessity for us to comply with legal obligations to establish, exercise, or defend
       ourselves from legal claims.
5.2.4. The necessity to pursue our legitimate interests, including, but not limited to:
5.2.4.1.   Improving the user experience and understanding how you behave on our Website
5.2.4.2.   Improving the security and performance of our Website
5.2.4.3.   To administer and generally conduct business within the Company
6.     Do We Collect Data From Children?
6.1.   EHTV does not knowingly collect personal data from children. The definition of “children”
       is subject to local and national laws and may vary accordingly.
7.     How Do We Use Cookies And Other Tracking Technologies?
7.1.   EHTV reserves the right to use so-called cookies. Cookies are alpha-numerical identifiers
       temporarily filed in the working memory ("Session Cookie") or permanently stored on the
       hard disk of the User's computer ("Permanent Cookie").
7.2.   Such information includes, but is not limited to, the User's IP address, login data, type
       and version of browser, the date and time when the User visits our Websites and a
       cookie number.
7.3.   The use of cookies enables EHTV to "recognize" the User at his/her next visit and to
       align the offer on the Websites and the Apps with the User's interests. Cookies are
       generally deleted once the User logs out of his personal account, or cookies expire on
       their dates of expiration. So-called language cookies which "recognize" the language of
       the Website previously used when the User visits the Website are not deleted when the

       User logs out. If the User does not log out of his personal account, all cookies are
       deleted after three months, at the latest.
7.4.   Withdrawal of Consent for the Use of 1st Party Cookies
7.4.1. At any time, users can delete their cookies from their browser through their browser
       settings. Additionally, EHTV deletes all 1st party cookies automatically after 6 weeks of
       setting. This period of 6 weeks is renewed anytime you visit our Website.
7.4.2. The type of cookies we may place on your browser can be clustered in three groups:
  Functional Cookies
   We make use of these cookies to ensure a good experience when browsing on our Website
  Analytics Cookies
   We make use of these cookies to measure user behavior.
  Marketing and Advertisement Cookies
   We work with advertisers and companies which helps us enable advertising on our Website.
   These companies may set certain cookies to understand your behavior and provide you with
   tailored advertising.
   You can find a list of all the cookies we place - both 1st and 3rd party cookies - on the
   following link: List of Cookies
8.     Withdrawal of Consent for the Use of Cookies
8.1.   You can opt-out from the use of marketing and analytics cookies by using the footer on
       our Website.
9.     Embedded Content and Share Links/Likes To Facebook, Twitter and Similar
9.1.   We may embed content from websites such as Facebook, Youtube, Twitter and similar
       on our Website. Pages with the embedded content may set cookies from the relevant
       website. We recommend that you check the relevant website for more information.
9.2.   When you use one of the share buttons on our Website or when you click on buttons
       contained within the embedded content on our Website, such as “Facebook like buttons”
       a cookie may be set on your browser by the relevant third-party. EHTV does not control
       the setting of these cookies and does not block the cookies from these websites. We
       recommend that you check the relevant website for more information.

10.    Who Do We Transfer Your Personal Data To?
10.1. There are several trusted partners we work with that process the personal data we
       collect. The partners are clustered in the following categories:
   User Statistics And Website Analytics Companies
   Functional Cookies Companies
   Payment Services
   Advertisers
11.    How Do We Secure Your Data?
11.1. EHTV uses all available technical and organizational security measures in order to protect
       your personal data against a breach of security leading to the accidental or unlawful
       destruction, loss, alteration, unauthorized disclosure of, or access to, your personal data
       transmitted, stored or otherwise processed.
11.2. EHTV employees are required to keep personal data confidential. EHTV employees will
       only transfer your personal data to third parties as described in Section 6 and 7 of this
       Notice.
12.    How Long Is My Data Kept?
12.1. EHTV does not keep personal data for longer than it is necessary for the purposes set
       out in Section 2 of this Notice.
12.2. For personal data that are not collected from cookies (see Section 3 of this Notice), we
       delete all personal data after 2 years of non-usage. That means, that if you have not
       logged in or have not consumed a service you have previously registered for a period of
       2 years, we delete your personal data. We may actively contact you before we delete the
       data.
12.3. For cookies, we delete all 1st party cookies (including your consent to use your personal
       data outside of functionalities that you actively have to register for) after 6 weeks of
       non-usage. That means, that if you have not visited our website for a period of more
       than 6 weeks, we delete all 1st party cookies.
13.    What Are My Rights?
13.1. EHTV reserves the right to refuse to give effect to a petitioner’s request in the event that
       we are unable to ascertain your identity.

13.2. Right to Access
      You have the right to obtain from EHTV a confirmation of whether EHTV is processing
      your data. Should EHTV process your data, you have the right to access your personal
      data and to obtain further information regarding the processing of your personal data.
13.3. Right to Rectification
      You have the right to have your personal data rectified by EHTV in the event that your
      personal data is inaccurate. You may also rectify the information by reviewing and
      changing the personal information on your account settings
13.4. Right to Erasure
      Under certain conditions, you have the right to have your personal data erased without
      delay. Those conditions are listed at article 17 of the GDPR.
13.5. Right to Restriction of Processing
      Under certain conditions, you have the right to restrict the processing of your personal
      data. Those conditions are listed at article 18 of the GDPR.
13.6. Right to Object to Processing
      Under certain conditions, you have the right to object to the processing of your personal
      data by EHTV. Those conditions are listed at article 21 of the GDPR.
13.7. Right to Data Portability
      You have the right to obtain your personal data in a structured, commonly used
      machine-readable format and to have your personal data transferred to another
      controller upon your request, and where technically feasible insofar as the processing of
      your personal data relies on your consent or it is necessary for the performance of a
      contract between you and EHTV
13.8. Right to Complain To a Supervisory Authority
      Should you believe that EHTV has infringed the applicable data protection laws, you have
      the right to file a complaint before the concerned Data Protection Authority.

13.9. Right to Withdraw Consent
      You may withdraw your consent to the processing of your personal data insofar as the
      processing relies on your consent. This does not apply if the processing is required for
      the performance of a contract between EHTV and you or if the processing is based on
      EHTV legitimate interests.
14.   Policy Changes
      EHTV reserves the right, at its discretion, to update, change, modify, add or amend this
      Policy by publishing a new version on our Website.
15.   Contact
      Should you have any questions regarding the processing of your personal data or should
      you wish to exercise a right as provided in Section of this Policy, please contact
      privacy@eurohockey.org
